<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>首页 on 日丰管潍坊总代理潍坊区域服务中心</title>
    <link>https://lg1024.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 首页 on 日丰管潍坊总代理潍坊区域服务中心</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>utf-8</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lg1024.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PPR管道</title>
      <link>https://lg1024.github.io/ppr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lg1024.github.io/ppr/</guid>
      <description>ppr给水管 Text can be **bold**, _italic_, or ~~strikethrough~~. [Links](https://github.com) should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).ppr暖气管道 There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs.There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs.欧标系列 &amp;gt; There should be no margin above this first sentence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PVC管道</title>
      <link>https://lg1024.github.io/pvc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lg1024.github.io/pvc/</guid>
      <description>PVC排水 Text can be **bold**, _italic_, or ~~strikethrough~~. [Links](https://github.com) should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).Text can be bold, italic, or strikethrough. Links should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).
PVC护套线管 There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs.There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>关于我们</title>
      <link>https://lg1024.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lg1024.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>日丰企业集团有限公司是中国新型塑料管道研发生产与推广应用的知名企业，中国给水管道升级、变革的重要推动者，是中国塑料加工工业协会塑料管道专业委员会副理事长单位，国家火炬计划重点高新技术企业，同时也是管道与卫浴全面发展的大型建材产业集团。
20世纪九十年代，日丰在国内率先引进欧洲先进的技术与设备，开启新型管道研发生产道路，逐步改变国内长期使用镀锌水管的现状，推动中国众多新型管道企业的兴起与行业变革，成为新型塑料管道行业的大型综合企业。
自公司成立以来，日丰一直将产品品质视为企业发展壮大的核心竞争力，坚持走品质为先的发展道路。日丰公司拥有国家认定企业技术中心、CNAS认证实验室等研发机构，获得600余项国内外专利，这些都为产品品质提供了的坚实保障。在涉及产品的原料选购、生产运输等环节，日丰公司严格加强把控，每一个工序，每一个细节，都做到精益求精。
日丰产品还通过美国NSF、德国SKZ等50多项国际认证，畅销全球的100多个国家和地区，荣获全球亿万用户一致认可与广泛赞誉。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>地暖管道</title>
      <link>https://lg1024.github.io/dinuan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lg1024.github.io/dinuan/</guid>
      <description>pert地暖管 Text can be **bold**, _italic_, or ~~strikethrough~~. [Links](https://github.com) should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).Text can be bold, italic, or strikethrough. Links should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).
pex-b地暖管 There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs.There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>日丰卫浴五金</title>
      <link>https://lg1024.github.io/weiyu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lg1024.github.io/weiyu/</guid>
      <description>日丰小五金 Text can be **bold**, _italic_, or ~~strikethrough~~. [Links](https://github.com) should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).Text can be bold, italic, or strikethrough. Links should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).
日丰卫浴 There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs.There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>首页</title>
      <link>https://lg1024.github.io/down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lg1024.github.io/down/</guid>
      <description>产品涵盖 日丰管材 供水管、排水管、电线管、地暖管、全屋前置过滤净水器，热水速达器等日丰卫浴 软管、龙头、角阀、地漏、浴室柜、马桶、淋浴房、厨房水槽、冷热混水龙头等施工对接 水电改造、铺地暖、暖气片负责人 李经理 18553659321</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>